zukureview.com 2015-12-26

# Privacy | Zukureview

## Online Privacy Policy for Zuku, LLC and www.zukureview.com

Thank you for visiting www.zukureview.com (the “Site”). The Site is a website owned, maintained, and operated by Zuku, LLC (“Zuku”). Zuku respects, and is strongly committed to protecting, the privacy and security of visitors to and members of the Site. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about the information we collect and how and why we use that information.

Zuku owns all intellectual property rights, title, and interest in the Site, the “ZukuReview” mark and logo, and our proprietary test preparation materials and content. By accessing or using the Site, you agree to comply with and be bound by the terms and conditions of our “Acceptable Use Policy”. http://zukureview.com/navle/disclaimer

## Personal Information Collection and Use

## Information Collected

The personal information we collect from users of our Site, and our use of the same information, depends on how you use our Site. We classify users of our Site three ways: (1) “ **Visitors** ” are users who simply access our Site; (2) “ **Registered Users** ” are users who register to receive our free “question of the day” email; and (3) “ **Subscribers** ” are users who register to pay for access to our complete test preparation materials. Subscribers also may register to receive our daily “question of the day” email. (Where appropriate, Registered Users and Subscribers will be referred to collectively as “ **Members** ” in this Privacy Policy.)

Zuku does not collect personal information from Visitors to the Site. 

A Visitor to the Site may register to become either a Registered User or a Subscriber. 

If you register as a Registered User, we will deliver to you our daily “question of the day” email and, as detailed below, certain communications and promotional offers.  Zuku will ask a Registered User for the following personal information: your name, email address, veterinary school, and year of graduation.

If you register as a Subscriber, you will receive access to our complete, proprietary test preparation materials, you may elect to receive our “question of the day” email, and, as detailed below, we may deliver to you certain communications and promotional offers.  Zuku will ask a Subscriber for the following personal information: your name, email address, veterinary school, year of graduation, mailing address, and telephone number. 

Finally, if you establish a credit account with Zuku or our third party providers, we collect additional information, including billing information; credit card number, authorization code, and expiration date as well as tracking information from any checks or money orders in order to service your account.

## Use of Information – Generally

The following describes the different ways Zuku uses personal information we collect from Registered Users and Subscribers.

Zuku will use the collected information solely for the purpose for which it was given.  Zuku will not sell or release any personal information collected from Registered Users or Subscribers without their express permission.  When you register as either a Registered User or a Subscriber, you can check the appropriate box and elect to “ **opt in** ” to receive our daily “question or the day” e-mails as well as: (1) email or text message communications from us that we believe may interest you such as alerts, notifications, newsletters, and surveys, or (2) to participate in promotional offers sponsored by us or our third party sponsors and advertisers.  By selecting the relevant box, you give us your express permission to Zuku to provide your name and e-mail address to a third party sponsoring the promotional offer.  Additionally, when you register, you will be asked to create a unique username and password.  After registering, you may change your preferences, username, or password by accessing your membership page and clicking on the “Edit My Profile” icon.

Any personal information we collect will be maintained and protected in accordance with the Privacy Act of 1974, as amended, 5 U.S.C. 552a (the “ **Privacy Act** ”). 

## Our Test Preparation Materials – Subscribers Only

Zuku will use information collected from Subscribers to: (1) make available to the Subscriber our proprietary test preparation materials; (2) to facilitate customization of a Subscriber’s individual test results; and (3) to access stored information if a Subscriber intends to utilize our test preparation materials. In addition to providing personalized results, the information that a Subscriber supplies at registration and through other communications with us is important for providing a Subscriber with specific instructional information related to our test preparation materials, for us to be able to communicate with a Subscriber, or to otherwise service a Subscriber’s account.

## Surveys

We may also ask Subscribers to participate voluntarily in our follow-up surveys so that you can rate the effectiveness of our test preparation materials and our Site’s features. Similarly, we may ask either Registered Users or Subscribers to participate in surveys regarding our Site or our sponsors or advertisers in order to enhance the usefulness of our Site. Participation in these surveys is voluntary and a Registered User or Subscriber has a choice of whether or not to disclose this information to us. Zuku may use survey information for its own internal purposes to monitor or improve the usability of the Site. Zuku also may share aggregated demographic information collected through surveys (that is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person) with our sponsors and advertisers.

## Promotional Offers

Periodically, Zuku also may deliver to our Members promotional offers through giveaways, contests, or other promotional events that we believe may be of interest to the Members, including promotions from Zuku’s sponsors or advertisers. Participation in a promotional offer may require disclosure by the Member of personal information such as name, email address, shipping address, school, and year of graduation. Participation in these promotional offers is voluntary and a Member has a choice of whether or not to disclose this information to us. In some instances, the promotional offer will be designed so that Zuku does not disclose a Member’s personal information to the sponsor or advertiser, but instead uses the information to deliver a promotional product or service on behalf of the sponsor or advertiser or to notify a winner and award prizes. In other instances, the promotional offer may require disclosure of a Member’s personal information to a sponsor or advertiser, but Zuku will do so only with the express consent of the affected Member. Zuku holds its sponsors and advertisers to the same rigorous standards of privacy and security that apply to Zuku, including being made subject to the Privacy Act, as applicable, and Zuku’s Privacy Policy.

## Cookies

Zuku may deposit cookies on a Visitor’s or Member’s hard drive. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Users who reject the cookie may still access and use the Site, but they may be limited in some areas of the Site.

Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our Visitors and Members to enhance their experience on out Site. Some of the information about how our users experience our Site, such as page views and specific pages visited, is logged by a third party company on our behalf, using cookies and web beacons. Web beacons help us understand information such as what browsers our users have so that we are able to develop our Site to best support our users. We control how this data may and may not be used.

## General Log Information

We collect certain non-personal information about your visit automatically. We limit this data collected to meet specific business needs and to fully protect your privacy. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not use this information to identify you personally without your express consent.

We automatically collect and store the following information about your visit to the Site:

  * Your internet domain and Internet Protocol (IP) address; the type of operating system you use; the browser used to access our Site; the date and time you access our Site; and the pages on our Site that you visit. We use IP addresses to administer the Site, analyze trends, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use; however, we do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information.
  * Referral and statistical information where we have links or advertisements to or from the Site. Such data may include aggregate data such as the number of clicks that occurred. It may also include specific data, such as whether you are a repeat Site user; whether you viewed or clicked on an advertisement and used our Site; and the identity of the website which you linked to or from our Site.

We use the general aggregated Site information to help us make our Site more useful to Visitors and Members by, for example customizing Site’s content, layout, and services; improving our content and service or product offerings; and statistically analyzing Site usage data and to improve our marketing and promotional efforts. We use it to learn about how the sections of our Site are being used, what information is of most or least interest, and how we may enhance ease of use by ensuring the Site can interface with the types of technology used by our Visitors and Members. We also use such statistics to tell us of any possible problems with the performance of the Site.

We collect referral statistics from links to let us know which links are useful, both to and from the Site. Likewise, we collect data from advertisements to let us know which ads are effective. This allows us to determine which ads may be of most interest and to help us control how many times a specific ad is displayed.

## Public Forums

Zuku may make it possible for our users to link to and share information through third party, public online spaces such as social networks, blogs, micro-blogs, reviews, surveys and discussion forums. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Consequently, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in this context.

## Security

For website security purposes and to ensure that our service remains available to all users, Zuku employs commercially available software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to change information, or otherwise cause damage. In those instances where we transmit your personal information between your browser and our server, we will encrypt the information using industry standard protocols such as Transport Layer Security (TLS) or Secure Socket Layer (SSL). The URL in your browser will change to "HTTPS" instead of "HTTP" when this security feature is in use. Your browser may also display a lock symbol on its bottom task bar line to indicate secure transmission.

Additionally, all users must have a unique username and password combination to gain access to the Members’ portion of the Site. You need to keep your password secret so that the personal information you have entered on the Site remains private. Our personnel will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. You should sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your session. This is to help ensure that others cannot access your personal information if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place where others may have access to it. Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, for example on message boards or in discussion forums, through e-mail, or in other areas, that information can be collected and used by others, as may the username and e-mail address that you use.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

If personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Zuku will promptly notify those users whose personal information may have been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits other than those uses identified in this Privacy Policy. Zuku will investigate intentional misuse of secure information on its Site and such investigation may result in federal prosecution.

## Privacy of Minors

If you are a minor under 18 years of age, then please do not use or access the Site at any time or in any manner. Zuku does not knowingly collect or maintain personal information through the Site from minors under 18 years of age, and no part of our Site is directed to minors under age 18. If Zuku learns that personally identifiable information of minors less than 18 years of age has been collected through the Site, then Zuku will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. Furthermore, if a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove this information. Additionally, the parent or guardian should attempt to access the minor’s membership page through clicking on the “Edit My Profile” button and uncheck the box for daily question e-mails to “opt out” of promotional opportunities.

## Transfer to the United States

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the personal data you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. Whenever you submit any personal data to us, you consent to this transfer.

## Third Party Practices

The privacy policy of a third party sponsor or advertiser on our Site may differ from our own Privacy Policy. When you click on links and ad banners that take you to third party websites or otherwise access another website to purchase products or services or to complete transactions, the use of any information that you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the third party website you are visiting or the provider of such products or services. We encourage you to read the third party’s privacy policy before responding to an offer for a product or service or otherwise completing a transaction.

## Other Disclosures

We may occasionally release information about our Visitors or Members when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our subscriber agreement, or to protect rights, property or the safety of users of our Site, the public, or our company and its employees, agents, partners and affiliates. As our business grows, we may purchase or sell various assets. If we choose to sell our company or the bulk of our assets relating to this Site, information on our Visitors and Members may be among the transferred assets. Changes to Our Policy

This Privacy Policy became effective on January 1, 2014 If we choose to update or modify this Privacy Policy, such updated or modified policy shall become effective five (5) business days after its posting on our Site. Accordingly, we encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy and our Site to keep apprised of our current privacy practices.

## Updating, Correcting or Deleting Your Information; Contacting Us

If you are a registered Member of our Site, you may review, correct, update or delete your personal data by clicking the “Edit My Profile” icon on your membership page. Alternatively, you can contact us at the mailing address, e-mail address or fax number as noted below. Your account can be deleted or deactivated, but doing so will result in your not being able to access subscriber services.

If you have any concerns about this Privacy Policy or our privacy or security practices in general, please contact us at:

Privacy Administrator  
Zuku, LLC  
2107 N. Decatur road, #426  
Decatur, Georgia 30033  
Phone: 1-800-928-8218  
Fax: 1-800-454-7140;

You can email us through our “Contact Us” link referenced on the home page of our Site.

_NAVLE® is a registered trademark owned by the National Board of Veterinary  Medical Examiners. This web site is not licensed by, endorsed by, or affiliated with the National Board of Veterinary Medical Examiners._
